Good afternoon, good day,
Добрый день
I’m from Ukraine, the city of Khmelnitsky, and
добрый я из Украины город Хмельницкий А
you are
вы
Vnukovo, the Moscow region, yes, you also
Внуково Московскую область да у вас тоже
don’t have electricity, like
света нет как у меня
I have everything, I don’t either, probably not
у нас все есть нет тоже Наверное нет
Because Russia woke us up, I’ve been
Потому что Россия нам разбудила я уже 7
sitting without electricity for 7 days, we are
дней сижу без света у нас вообще
completely turned off as I understand it  that you,
отключена полностью Я так понял что вам
too, were bombed somewhere by us. You, too, are
тоже где-то наши бомбили Вы тоже
probably sitting without light
наверное без света сидите
or not with the light. What about in the dark,
или нет со светом сижу А что в темноте
but the TV does not work;
но у телевизора работает это работает
I believe Yes, I
блин точно понял все Теперь верю Да я
thought you were deceiving us because I
думал вы обманываете потому что нам я
don’t see the News like that anymore, I can’t
Новостей так не вижу больше не могу
read it to me, they told me that it’s also in
почитать мне говорили что там тоже это в
Belgorod in Belgorod, our
Белгороде в Белгороде бомбили наши
power supply was bombed, you sit without light, you
электропоставление сидишь без света
charge it like charging a generator, a
заряжаешь как заряжая генератор
bicycle, a bicycle, a generator over there
велосипед велосипеда генератор вон там в
in my garden is standing,
саду у меня стоит
but here  look at how you feel about a
а вот смотрите вы как относитесь к
special military
специальной военной операции
operation. Why Putin, I can’t nobody
А почему Путин я не могу никто
Putin is a kind and patient person,
Путин человек добрый и терпеливый
you probably understand very well what it
вы прекрасно понимаете наверное Что
means  it’s to declare war I know Yes, just
значит объявить войну Я знаю Да просто
if he declares war immediately Ukraine
если он объявит войну сразу же Украина
will have beaver business trips to Vnukovo in the
будет бобровые командировки Внуково
Belgorod region to do you then
Белгородской области делать вам тогда
Kapets, that’s why he’s afraid,
Капец он поэтому и боится
you think so Well, yes, when
ты так считаешь Ну да Когда объявляется
war is declared, everything is closed by the border and
война закрывается все границей и
there is no transit, no money, nothing but
никакого не транзита ни денег ничего а
to bomb Belgorod  there is still there
чтобы бомбили Белгород там еще там
to walk Voronezh or something else there is
ходить Воронеж или еще что-то есть
heavy no the Americans will give us
тяжелый нет нам американцы дадут
closed borders now we have something
закрыты границы сейчас у нас что-то есть
across the borders
через границы
oil goes gas goes electricity goes
нефть идет газ идет электричество идет
Well you solarium Where do you get the reserves were the
Ну ты соляру Где ты берешь запасы были
reserves Where does it come from Europe
запасы Откуда она вообще из Европы
Europe does it come from  in Belarus In
Европы она идет в Беларуси У нас в
Belarus, at first, the wars stopped deliveries in Belarus.
Беларуси сначала войны прекратили
So they
те Так говорят
say I just have no news for 7 days,
у меня просто 7 дней нету новостей
so I’m not quite up to date,
поэтому я не совсем курсе
it turns out that Putin He
смотрите получается что Путин Он
absolutely understands that such a steel
абсолютно понимает что такая сталая
country like Russia, it
страна как Россия она против НАТО против
can’t do anything against NATO, and therefore
Америки не может ничего и поэтому Если
Unless  he will announce, well, he understands this. We,
только он объявит ну он это понимает Мы
as pawns of the North Atlantic Alliance,
как пешки Север Атлантического Альянса
will give us the weapons we need, we will smash  what for
нам дадут нужно оружие мы разбом нафиг
your Vnukovo is there Belgorod Voronezh,
ваши Внуково там Белгород Воронеж
therefore Putin is afraid to declare war,
поэтому Путин боится объявить войну
we need Putin to declare, we
нам надо чтобы Путин объявил было у нас
had an excuse We are not terrorists like
был предлог Мы же не террористы как
Putin, we can just take and bomb our
Путин мы можем просто взять и разбомбить
grandchildren, you understand Well, you bomb your grandchildren
внуков понимаете Ну вы же бомбите внуков
no
нет
Belgorod closely understand Belgorod
Белгород близко понимаете Белгород
close it’s like an answer arrives  it flies from there
близко это как ответки прилетает оттуда
and flies to us, but in order to
летит и нам летит а вот чтобы Внуково
shoot Vnukovo We need an excuse And you will eat everything,
пальнуть Нам нужен предлог А все гулять
they will give it Yes, the Americans
будете есть дадут дадут Да американцы
will give everything for the sake of this, you didn’t think such a
дадут все ради такого ты не думал такую
topic has been there for how many
тему там уже сколько там
years 8 they give give give Will give back who’s
лет 8 дают дают дают Будет отдавать кто
debts Will give back to the Americans you
долги Будет отдавать американцам вы
will give
будете отдавать репарации
I taught reparations like that no I came up with it myself I
я так научили нет сам придумал сам
came up with education the first
придумал образование первое
programmer of lawyers a
программистор юристов
lawyer something a lawyer doesn’t look like you in a
юрист что-то юрист не похожи по твоему в
hat it’s not that I don’t see you at all you’re in
шапке не это я тебя не вижу ты вообще в
some kind of sharpness No I probably sealed it
каком-то резкости Нет наверно заклеил
just darkly so I see
просто темно поэтому я же вижу резкости
there’s no sharpness and with a wall  or it’s not warmly closed the
нет причем стеной или не тепло закрыл
camera, you’re afraid to openly look
камеру боишься вот открыто смотрите
at you at all,
у тебя вообще ничего
maybe you’re a fool, this could
Может ты дурачок такое может быть
be  Nadia just wants
и Нади просто хочется
diarrhea of ​​the lodge, you know,
поноса лоджи вот из таким знаете
trolling and 2000 Yak people on the other
троллингом и 2000 Як у людей по ту
side of the curb get burned and everyone
сторону поребрика подгорает он и все
understands their worthlessness so
понимает свою никчемность такой так и
when you start just for the top
когда ты начинаешь просто за верхнюю
data so rates and you know
данных так ставок и знаете
internal internal burning can be
внутренний внутренний подгорания бывает
even more than the simplest
еще чем простейшие
farts you mean
пуканчики ты значит
an indicator of that now the eyebrows of Ukraine for the
индикатор того сейчас брови Украины за
petrynka of our allies
петрынки наших союзники
on the channel
на канал
they are not farted a word in Ukraine
их не пуканы слово в Украине